Guide to the Toni Beauchamp Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Other Works, id166259
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston/Harris County, id166538
    - Career Development Opportunities/Candidates, id166589
      - Eleanor Fink, 1997-1999; id166699 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Professional Consultant/Professional Development, id166590
      - Contracts and Services, 1984; id166701 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Search Firms, 1998-1999; id166702 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Public Art, id166591
      - History, 1981; id166704 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - The Art League of Houston, 1995; id166705 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Sculpture, 1984-1985; id166706 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - References, undated; id166707 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - HOV Music Hall FND– Hobby Center, 1998-2001; id166708 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, 1992; id166709 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Houston Packets, 1992-1995; id166710 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Houston, 1990-1995; id166711 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Private Funding, 1988-1992; id166712 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Symposium, 1981-1986; id166713 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Task Force, 1991-1992; id166714 (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston (MFA,H), id166539
    - MFA,H, id169611
      - Booklet, 1996; id166716 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Panel, 1987; id166717 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - The Collectors, 1984-1991; id166718 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Contribution, 1982-1989; id166719 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Florescence, 1997; id166720 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Photo Forum, 1993-1994; id166721 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Design Council, 1998-2004; id166722 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - MFA,H, 1970-2005; id166723 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Various, undated; id166724 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Glassell School of Art, id166725
      - MFA,H Glassell School, 1996-2010; id166727 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Critical Writing Fellow, 1997-1998; id166728 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Peter Szatmary, 1998-1999; id166729 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Core Friends, 2001-2010; id166730 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Core Committee, 1998-2007; id166731 (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
  - Contemporary Arts Museum Houston, id166540
    - History, undated; id166735 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - CAM,H Contributions, 1990-1999; id166736 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Accreditation Hand Book, undated; id166737 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Committee, 2000; id166738 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Funding, 1980-1990; id166739 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Collectors Circle Correspondence, 1993-1994; id166740 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2004; id166741 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Board of Director’s Notes, 1996-1998; id166742 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Executive Director Search, 1994; id166743 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Trustee Slate, undated; id166744 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Member Info, 2000-2002; id166745 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - CAM,H Ref– Rosters, 1987-2002; id166746 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Rosters, 1995-2005; id166747 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Charles Desmaris, 1994; id166748 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Collector’s Circle, 1990-1992; id166749 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
    - Collector’s Circle, 1980; id166751 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - By-laws and Trustee List, 1984-1992; id166752 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1987-1991; id166753 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Public Information Committee, 1988; id166754 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Christmas Party, 1988-1989; id166755 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Board of Trustees– Expired, 1985-1991; id166756 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Development Committee, 1986-1991; id166757 (Box 23, Folder 23-24)
    - Artist Books Project, 1990-1991; id166759 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Economic Summit, 1990; id166760 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - General Reference– Correspondence, 1986-1992; id166761 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Annual Program Fund, 1986-1987; id166762 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence / Faxes, 1994; id166763 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Dinner Honoring Pieter Laurens Mol, 1994; id166764 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Contemporary Art of Texas: The Styles of Art and How it is Supported Booklet, undated; id166765 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Search Committee, 1994; id166766 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - CAM,H, undated; id166767 (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
  - The Menil Collection, id166541
    - The Menil Strategic Plan, undated; id166769 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Friends of The Menil, 1982-2010; id166770 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - The Menil Collection (works), undated; id166771 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Financial Statements, 1999-2001; id166772 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Rothko Chapel and Spiritual Centers, 2000; id166773 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Booklet Les Fanantiques (A Look at the Lives of John & Dominique de Menil), undated; id166774 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Various Houston: Menil Collection, undated; id166775 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
  - Orange Show, id166542
    - Various Orange Show Invitations, undated; id166777 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Various Orange Show Overview, undated; id166778 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Marketing Committee, 2001; id166779 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Americans for the Arts, id166543
    - Research, undated; id166781 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Literatures / Speeches / Position Papers, 2000-2003; id166782 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Floppy Disc, Arts Advocacy Day, 2000; id166783 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Printed Materials, 2002-2003; id166784 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Ref, 1987; id166785 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Various, 1995-1998; id166786 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Art Resources of Texas (ART), id166544
    - Projects, undated; id166788 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Organizational Paper, 2001; id166789 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Houston Arts Exhibition, id166545
    - Juried Art Competition / Art Exhibit Text, 1980; id166791 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Catalogue, undated; id166792 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Texas Arts Inventory, id166546
    - Arts and Artists, undated; id166794 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Art Museums, undated; id166795 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Artist Biographies / Ref, undated; id166796 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, id166547
    - Conference, 1994; id166798 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
    - Sesquicentennial Commission, 1983-1984; id166799 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1998; id166800 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Controversy, 1992; id166801 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - National Association for Artist Organization, 1987-1992; id166802 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Printouts, 1995; id166803 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Panel, 1991-1992; id166804 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Arts Taskforce Overview, 1993-1994; id166806 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Arts Taskforce Reference Material, undated; id166807 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Art Table, id166548
    - Membership / Nominations, 1996-2005; id166809 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - National Profile, Women in the Visual Arts, undated; id166810 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Resumes, 2007; id166811 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Member Directories, 1996-2004; id166812 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
    - Various Printouts, 1998-2001; id166813 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - undated, id166814 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Watermill Center, Byrd Hoffman Foundation (Robert Wilson), id166549
    - History, 1999-2001; id166817 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Water Mill Project, 1994-2001; id166818 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Printouts, undated; id166819 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Press Package / Patron List, 2001; id166820 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Taxes / Correspondence, undated; id166821 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Solicitation Letters, 1993-1994; id166822 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Miscellanea / Clippings, undated; id166823 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Contributions, 1993-2004; id166824 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Reference Files, id166550
    - Historic Preservation, 1994; id166826 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Galleries, undated; id166827 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Folk Art, undated; id166828 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Craft Gallery / Furniture, undated; id166829 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Museums, undated; id166830 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Museology, undated; id166831 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Corporate Houston, 1991-1993; id166832 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Print-Outs, 1976-2000; id166833 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Profiles, 1983; id166834 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Architecture, 1989; id166835 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Art History– Modern, 1983-2001; id166836 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Attorneys Reference / Bio, 1995-2003; id166837 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Corporate Art, 1979-1999; id166838 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Biographical Info / VIPs, 1996-1997; id166839 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Exhibit– Collin, undated; id166840 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Art Reference, undated; id166841 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, 1985; id166842 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Leadership Houston, id166551
    - Directory, 2001-2005; id166844 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Roster, 1986-1992; id166845 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Arts Day, 1995; id166846 (Box 26, Folder 26-27)
    - Program Committee, 1986-1989; id166848 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Program Committee, 1994-1995; id166849 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Cultural Diversity of Houston, 1986-1987; id166850 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Class, 1985-1986; id166852 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Sesquicentennial– Bayou Event, 1986; id166853 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Baxte and Associates, 1986-1987; id166854 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - TB, 1985-1988; id166855 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Publications, 1985-1986; id166856 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter, 1986-1987; id166857 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Communications Committee, 1986-1987; id166858 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Arts Committee, 1992-1993; id166859 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Current Program, 1985-1986; id166860 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Cultural Life, 1986; id166861 (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
    - Reference Material, 1994-1995; id166862 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Various, 1984-1986; id166863 (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
  - Philanthropy, id166552
    - Correspondence, id166864
      - Farrel Dyde Dance Theatre, 1997; id166869 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - HGO– Vanguard, 1990-1996; id166870 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Barnes-Blackman Galleries, 1993; id166871 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Bill White, 2003; id166872 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Political Contributions, 1989-2003; id166873 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - George Grenias, 1990-1997; id166874 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Ken Bentsen Campaign, 1994-2000; id166875 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Greater Houston Preservation Alliance, 1994-1995; id166876 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Stages, 1984-1992; id166877 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Act for 8, 2003; id166878 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Houston REF, 1990; id166879 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Contributors, id166865
      - The Chinati Foundation / La Fundación Chinati, 2005-2006; id166882 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - ArtLies, 2004; id166883 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - FotoFest, 1986; id166884 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Friends of Hermann Park, undated; id166885 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Artadia, undated; id166886 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Memberships and Contributions Under Consideration, 1994-2001; id166887 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Various Contributions, undated; id166888 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Associations, id166866
      - Folk Art Society, 1998; id166890 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Baker Institute at Rice, 1998-2000; id166891 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Artpace, 2002-2004; id166892 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Art Table, 2003-2004; id166893 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Asia Society, 1994-2011; id166894 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Special Events, id166867
      - Hospice, undated; id166896 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Center for the Performing Arts, undated; id166897 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Rice University, id166553
    - Art Gallery, 1997-2003; id166899 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Art Deptartment, 2002; id166900 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Rice Design Alliance, 1981-2003; id166901 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Events Around Houston, id166554
    - Art History, 1963-2004; id166903 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Architecture / Historical Information, undated; id166904 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Artists, undated; id166905 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Galleries, 1980-2000; id166906 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Grand Opera of Houston, 1995; id166907 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Houston Museum of Natural Science, 2003; id166908 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - City of Houston, 1995; id166909 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Houston International Protocol Alliance, 1990-1995; id166910 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Composers Circle / Houston Symphony, 1990-1997; id166911 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - General, 1990-2004; id166912 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Brazos Books, id166555
    - Distribution, 2001-2005; id166914 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Various Books, 1996-2005; id166915 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Promotional Materials, undated; id166916 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Artpace San Antonio, id166556
    - Annual Report, 1995; id166920 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - HOV (Project), 1997; id166921 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Database, id166557
    - Library Database, 1999; id166923 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Houston Database, 1997-1998; id166924 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Blueprint Houston, id166558
    - History, 2002-2003; id166926 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Memorandum, 2002-2003; id166927 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - League of Women Voters, id166559
    - Handbook and Directory, 1993; id166929 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Study Action, 1992-1993; id166930 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Business Volunteers for the Arts (BVA), id166560
    - Houston Resource Material Handbook, undated; id166932 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Orientation Notebook, 1985; id166933 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Various, 1981-1987; id166934 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), id166561
    - History, 1993-1995; id166936 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Hospitality, 1998; id166937 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Sweeney Archive Support Material, id166562
    - Professional Travel, 1980-1983; id166941 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Libraries: Collections and Reference, undated; id166942 (Box 29, Folder 11-12)
    - UT Thesis Information, 1980-1983; id166944 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Thesis Correspondence, 1981-1987; id166945 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - UT: Museums and Collections, undated; id166946 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Bibliographies, 1980-1982; id166947 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Sent to Linda– Final Draft, 1983; id166948 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Methodology Class Notes, undated; id166949 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Toni Beauchamp Master’s Thesis Original Draft, 1983; id166950 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - General Reference Vol VIII– Art in America, undated; id166951 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Interviews Vol VI– Various, undated; id166952 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Houston General Vol VII, undated; id166953 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Sources Vol X, undated; id166954 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Research Materials– In Progress, undated; id166955 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report– Budget, 1965-1969; id166956 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence– Gisptein, 1982; id166957 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - James Johnson Sweeney as Author Vol I, 1930-1961; id166958 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
    - Sweeney at Guggenheim Vol II, 1951-1959; id166959 (Box 30, Folder 8-9)
    - MFA, H Vol III, 1953-1969; id166960 (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
    - Vol IV. Sweeney and MFA,H– James Johnson Sweeney Acquisitions, 1961-1967; id166961 (Box 30, Folder 12-14)
    - Vol IV.B Sweeney and MFA,H– MFA,H Board/Budget, James Johnson Sweeney, General, 1961-1967; id166962 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
    - Archives of American Art, 1983-1984; id166963 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Text Conference of Art Historians, 1979; id166964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Museum of Fine Arts Exhibits, 1929-1980; id166965 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Selected Sweeney Acquisitions and Exhibitions, 1967-1967; id166966 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - James John Sweeney and Museum of Fine Arts Houston, 1961-1967; id166967 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Music and Art Distribution: Reference Papers and Research Notes, 1952-1983; id166968 (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
    - Sweeney Vol. V, 1968-1982; id166969 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Sothebys, 1984-1986; id166970 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Various, 1968; id166971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Toni Beauchamp Master’s Thesis, 1983; id166973 (Ovsbox 1, Item 2)
  - Research Materials and Art History Paper, id166563
    - Bat Imagery in Classic Mayan Ceramics, 1980; id166976 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - The 20th Century American Art: The Armory Show to the Present, 1981; id166977 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Index of the Introduction to Modern Perspective in Western Art History, undated; id166978 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - UCLA Conference of Professional Arts Managers, 1978; id166979 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Toni Beauchamp University of Texas Austin’s Personal Lecture Notebooks, undated; id166980 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Centaur Imagery: A Notebook, 1980; id166982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - VIII Rembrandt, undated; id166983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - The Centaur Iconography, undated; id166984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Dutch Mannerist 16th century, undated; id166985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - David and Goliath, undated; id166986 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Early Christians, 1960; id166987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Mayan Bats, undated; id166988 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Leonardo da Vinci– Battle of Anghiari, 1980; id166989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Various Selected Historical Articles, undated; id166990 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
    - Toni’s Art History Papers, 1973-1979; id166991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Cultural Exchange Foundation, The Netherlands, id166564
    - Overview / Government Relations, 1986; id166993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Reference Materials, 1986-1989; id166994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Memorandums / Articles, 1987-1989; id166995 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Articles, 1987; id166996 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors Meetings / Minutes of Meetings, 1987-1989; id166997 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Publications, 1987; id166998 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Houston Arts Festival, id166565
    - Visual Arts Panel, 1980-1982; id167001 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Bayou Show– Artist, 1984; id167002 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Visual Art Committee, 1984; id167003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising, 1984; id167004 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Notebook– Meeting Minutes / Correspondence, 1982-1986; id167005 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
  - Harvard University, id166566
    - Various Personal Notes and Printouts, 1975-1978; id167007 (Box 33, Folder 5-7)
  - Personal and Professional Affiliations, id166567
    - Intermat, 1991-1995; id167009 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Lamar High School Alumni, 2002-2003; id167010 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Art League, 1974-1979; id167011 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Alternative Spaces, 1984-2000; id167012 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - American Leadership Forums, 1989-1995; id167013 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - American Leadership Forums, 1993-1994; id167014 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Arts Association and Chamber of Commerce, 1973-1991; id167015 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Amnesty International, 2003; id167016 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Harris County Heritage Society, 1984-1994; id167017 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Library of Congress Museum Loans, 1994; id167018 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Independent Curators, Incorporated, 1994; id167019 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Texas Fine Arts Associations, 1995-2000; id167020 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Women’s Caucus for Art, 1978; id167021 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Corporate Directors, 1986; id167022 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Richard Newlin– Houston Fine Arts Press, 1988; id167023 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - ARTSPAC, 1993-1994; id167024 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Coca Cola Foods / Grover Jackson, 1987; id167025 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Ballroom MARFA, 2003-2008; id167026 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - The Grantsmanship, undated; id167027 (Box 33, Folder 26-27)
    - Alley Theatre, undated; id167028 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Various Funding and Foundations, id166568
    - Houston Philanthropy, 1997-2001; id167030 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Grant, 1991; id167031 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Donald Judd / Chinati, 1995-2010; id167032 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Pace Roberts Foundation– San Antonio, 1994-1997; id167033 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Greater Houston Women’s Foundation, 1999-2000; id167034 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Houston Grand Opera, 1988-1989; id167035 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chinati Art and Architecture Symposium, 1998; id167036 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Various Projects, id166569
    - Costswold, 1997-1998; id167038 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - TURREL: Live Oak Friends Meeting House, 1997-2002; id167039 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Stephen Klineberg, 1996-2000; id167040 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Lee Mingwei, 2002; id167041 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - International Waterfront Center Cape May NJ, 2003-2010; id167042 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Moody Park, 1994; id167043 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Project Row Houses– Rick Lowe, 1997-2002; id167044 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Pine Hill Residence, undated; id167045 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Various Professional Consultant/Professional Development, id166570
    - Eric Bricker, 2010; id167047 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - W. M. A. Robinson– Art Consultant, 1984-1998; id167048 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Management Consultants for the Arts, undated; id167049 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Real Estate Investment, 1982; id167050 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Art Center / Warehouse, 1983; id167051 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Secretary, 1994; id167052 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Pierce Kennedy Marketing Strategy, 1991-1992; id167053 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Special Events, id166571
    - Lawndale Anniversary, 1992-2003; id167056 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Community Center, 1967-1979; id167057 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - MAC, 1989; id167058 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Blue Star San Antonio, 1995; id167059 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Holocaust Museum, 1996; id167060 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Susman Anti-Defamation League Lunch, 1995; id167061 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Private Collections– Houston, 2000-2002; id167062 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - International Women’s Year, 1974-1977; id167063 (Box 34, Folder 30-31)
    - International Women’s Year, 1974-1977; id167064 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, id166572
    - The Museum of Modern Art, New York, NY, 2000-2004; id167066 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Marfa Arts Organizations, 2004-2010; id167067 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Rodger and Tricia Winn, 2007; id167068 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Sharon Lorenzo, 1983-2000; id167069 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Carol H. Neuberger, 1994-2006; id167070 (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
    - Jason Gray, 1995; id167071 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Gordon Shepperd, 1998; id167072 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Jordy Tollett, 1997-1998; id167073 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Bill Camfield, 2010; id167074 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Stephen Fox, 1995-2009; id167075 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Tanya Eagle, 1994-1995; id167076 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Kevin Cunningham, 1995; id167077 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Katy Butter Nick, 1999; id167078 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Steinway “A” Piano, 1987-1998; id167079 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - High School for Performing and Visual Arts, 1993; id167080 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Personal Correspondence, undated; id167081 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Various Printed Material, Publications, Articles, id166573
    - Conference of Professional Arts Managers, 1978; id167083 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - For Your Information, 1985-1986; id167084 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Art Law and Accounting Reporter, 1982-1987; id167085 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Grantsmanship, 1976-1979; id167086 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Missouri Arts Council, 1998-2000; id167087 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Bottom Line, 1992; id167088 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, undated; id167089 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Imprints, 2000-2002; id167090 (Box 35, Folder 26)